It's important when you pick your board size to choose something that's going to really work for you in your life.
If you have a goal and you want to have a vision board that you're going to carry with you.
You may want to pick up a little index card.
You don't have to make a vision board big in order for it to be effective.
You just have to have it in a place where you're going to be able to see it.
Some things you may want to do small.
One of my favorite things to do is recycle.
Sometimes, I take envelopes that people have sent me and I use the front part for the vision board because I cover it with a lot of things.
Then thing I love is that you can put stuff inside and hide it.
We'll be talking about that later.
That's a good way to do things.
They're kind of fun, because the mailing envelopes, you can get, they're usually in really varied sizes.
Sometimes you get big things, sometimes you get little things.
You can always use cardboard if you want to use that.
If you want something square.
You can make a round vision board if you want to cut it.
Then, I really like bright, bright colors.
You can go and you can get construction paper from someplace.
You can either, I like folding things in half so I can put things in, but you can buy these at any kind of, you know, supply place or something.
You can have it folded in half and then you're able to use a vision board.
The most important thing when you're choosing your size is to make sure you know what you want to be able to do.
Do you want it at your desk?
Do you want it at your office?
Do you want to keep it at home by your bedroom?
Depending on the goal that you've chosen and the topic that you're doing.
You may want to have a smaller board if you want something that you're going to see when you're taking a shower.
You may put it in something where it's water proof.
Really kind of think about where do you want this to be in your life and how do you want to keep it with you so that you can make sure that you've got the right size for your vision.